{
    "subject": "resource/Randy_Quaid",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Quaid, Randy",
    "human_readable": "The name of Randy Quaid is Quaid, Randy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9479280710220337,
            "question": "What is Randy Quaid's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.934408962726593,
            "question": "What is Randy Quaid's last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.914466917514801,
            "question": "Is 'Quaid' Randy Quaid's given or family name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.911091685295105,
            "question": "What is the first name of Randy Quaid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8647094964981079,
            "question": "What order are the names listed in for Randy Quaid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.853138267993927,
            "question": "What is the relationship between 'Quaid' and 'Randy' in his full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8515545129776001,
            "question": "How would you list Randy Quaid's name formally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7707168459892273,
            "question": "Can you provide Randy Quaid's name using reverse order?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5471053719520569,
            "question": "If someone wanted to address Randy Quaid directly, what would they say?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46252313256263733,
            "question": "If someone was looking up Randy Quaid's information, what would they likely search for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Randy Quaid is Quaid, Randy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7376_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone wanted to address Randy Quaid directly, what would they say?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7376_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide Randy Quaid's name using reverse order?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7376_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you list Randy Quaid's name formally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7376_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7376_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7376_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7376_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7376_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7376_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7376_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7376_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7376_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7376_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7376_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Randy Quaid's full name, which includes his first and last names, confirming that his name is indeed \"Quaid, Randy\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Randy Quaid's full name as Randall Rudy Quaid and refer to him as \"Randy Quaid,\" which supports the triple stating that his name is Quaid, Randy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states his full name is Randall Rudy Quaid, meaning \"Quaid\" is his last name.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}